A Guide to the American Rhododendron Society Papers
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #10553-o
American Rhododendron Society Papers 1973-1988
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
10553-o
ca. 15 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift, 1989 January 16
Container List
- Breeder's Roundtable Proceedings, 1973 May 27
- Breeder's Roundtable Proceedings, 1974
- Hybridizer's Symposium, East Coast, 1975 Mar 1
- Hybridizer's Roundtable, 1976 May 23
- Hybridizer's Meeting Proceedings, 1979 Sep 15
- Chapter Information, 1984-1987
- "Comprehensive Rhododendron Show Schedule"
- Correspondence, 1985, 1988
- Glasgow Garden Festival, 1988
- "A List of Rhododendron Cultivar Names Registered ... Since 1958", 1976
- Printed Material, 1985-1988
- "Rhododendrons in the British Isles - An Irreverent Approach" by Dan E. Mayers, ca. 1977